<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><modules><module><id><![CDATA[1015]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedpack]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Pack 5]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Перекрестные продажи и Создание комплектов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Продажа пакетов товаров с учетом наличия на складе и возможность проводить бизнес-операции]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/cross-selling-product-bundles/1015-advanced-pack-5.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1015.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Продажа пакетов товаров с учетом наличия на складе и возможность проводить бизнес-операции.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Возможность закупать дополняющие друг друга товары со скидкой или без нее одним нажатием  Хотите увеличить среднюю корзину и при этом позволить своим клиентам экономить, если они приобретают несколько товаров одновременно? Теперь это возможно благодаря модулю Advanced Pack! Вы сэкономите время, сможете создать пакеты товаров, которые можно будет купить всего одним нажатием, и вам не придется беспокоиться о наличии на складе или о дополняющих товарах.  Дополнительный ценный инструмент продаж Помогайте своим клиентам совершать покупки. Предлагайте им пакеты дополняющих товаров, которые вы составите заранее, так же как это делают продавцы в обычных магазинах. Например, этот замечательный фотоаппарат, карта памяти и треножник. Очевидно, что эти товары дополняют друг друга, и это заинтересует клиентов.  Или можете выставлять товары, которые продаются лучше всего, вместе с теми, которые менее популярны, чтобы клиенты увидели их.  В ваших пакетах может быть сколько угодно товаров, но не менее двух. Выберите количество каждого товара, а затем дополняющие товары на свой вкус. Вариантов приумножить возможности масса.  Хотите отложить покупку определенного товара из пакета? Это тоже возможно! Таким образом, вы сможете предложить бесплатный товар, если он будет приобретен в составе пакета. Возможностей множество! Встроенный помощник Не всегда очевидно, какие именно товары стоит включать в пакет. И здесь опять же вам поможет модуль Advanced Pack. При создании пакета модуль будет предоставлять вам такие важные сведения, как количество проданных товаров или их наличие на складе. В ваш пакет также встроен динамический симулятор цен, который поможет лучше понять, когда стоит совершить сделку, не навредив прибыли. Станьте экспертом по дополняющим товарам  Один из добавленных в пакет товаров доступен в нескольких цветах, но вы не хотите предлагать их все в одном наборе? Вам поможет модуль Advanced Pack.  Вы также сможете заранее продумать дополняющие товары по умолчанию для каждого товара пакета, даже если они отличаются от указанных в вашем каталоге.  Тогда ваши клиенты смогут выбрать то, что им захочется, среди параметров, которые вы включите в предложение.  Бизнес-мотивация  Мотивация — это то, что побуждает вашего посетителя сделать покупку. Главная задача — убедить как можно больше посетителей оформить заказ, и/или чтобы они потратили больше денег за сделку. Возможно, вы уже пробовали предлагать бесплатную доставку при определенной стоимости покупок и скидки на определенные товары или даже рассылали скидочные купоны? Все эти методы работают, но их возможности ограничены, так как эти акции временны из-за чрезмерных затрат! Хватит искать, решение уже нашлось!  Для стимулирования покупок модуль Advanced Pack предоставит выбор по применению скидки, когда все товары в корзине будут заказаны, что побудит клиентов приобрести весь пакет.  Доступны 3 возможности:Предложить определенную скидку на каждый товар из пакета.Применить общую скидку на набор товаров.Применить фиксированную цену, учитывая психологию покупателей например.Модуль Advanced Pack также позволяет управлять скидками, которые уже были применены к вашим товарам. Таким образом, вы сможете учесть их в цене пакета или, наоборот, вычесть, чтобы выбрать заранее заданную скидку на пакет. Принимать решения будет еще проще благодаря четкому и интуитивно понятному интерфейсу, найти товары со скидкой в котором не составит труда.  Больше не придется переживать о несовпадающих ценах  Приходилось ли вам когда-нибудь пересматривать все цены в каталоге, чтобы выявить и исправить возможные несовпадения? Что если бы вам пришлось вручную устранять последствия изменений в ценах товаров из пакетов? Если это не было запланировано в ваших решениях по управлению пакетами, то стало бы значительной сверхурочной нагрузкой! Напоминаем, что с помощью модуля Advanced Pack можно решить эту проблему. По умолчанию, если цена пакета не была снижена, то она складывается из цен входящих в него товаров. Как только вы измените цену товара после создания пакета, цена пакета изменится автоматически без вашего участия. В тех случаях, когда вы примените скидку на один или более товаров из существующего пакета, при условии что вы имеете права на такие рекламные изменения, цена за пакет будет также изменена, а клиенты увидят, какая была применена скидка.  Товар из вашего пакета подпадает под экологический налог? Нет проблем — это будет автоматически четко указано в цене пакета в полном соответствии с законодательством. Все, что касается управления вашим складом, автоматизировано! Каждый заказанный пакет будет автоматически убран со склада, на котором хранился. Таким образом, вы избежите двойной проверки складов и проблем, связанных с несоответствием количества. Кроме того, когда товара из пакета не окажется на складе, он будет автоматически отображаться как недоступный для покупки, благодаря новейшей системе предупреждения о наличии.  Для ваших клиентов мы внедрили наглядную удобную систему, которая сразу же оповещает о малом количестве дополняющих товаров или товаров, входящих в пакет. Будьте уверены: никто не закажет товары, которых нет на складе!  Выделите пакеты и продайте больше После того как вы оформите пакет, вы сможете настроить его так же, как и классический товар. Можно выбрать для него любое изображение, внести его в любую категорию, оптимизировать для поиска, добавить описание, присвоить EAN-код или определенный номер, задать объем для расчета стоимости доставки и не только.  Для сжатого представления и для более эффективной рекламы модуль Advanced Pack автоматически отобразит все фотографии товаров пакета, а также их табличные описания. Ваши клиенты получат нужную информацию, не покидая страницы пакета, и смогут оформить покупку одним нажатием.  Но это не все... Для большей наглядности ваши пакеты будут автоматически выделяться в описаниях, если продаются партиями. Таким образом, вы побудите клиентов заказать пакет целиком вместо одного товара, который они собирались приобрести. По большому счету, это сопутствующие продажи: доступный способ увеличения средней покупательской корзины! Мы позаботились и о дизайнерах  Изначально мы позаботились о том, чтобы этот модуль могли без труда приспосабливать как веб-агентства, так и дизайнеры либо специалисты по интеграции. Модуль прекрасно приспосабливается к темам по умолчанию PrestaShop 1.5 и 1.6, предоставляя при этом наиболее расширенные возможности графической настройки. В состав модуля входят набор шаблонов JavaScript и таблиц стилей CSS, которые повысят эффективность внедрения. Таким образом, вы или специалист по интеграции можете пользоваться полными возможностями движка Advanced Pack 5, чтобы графически воплотить то, что будет в лучшей мере соответствовать общему стилю вашего интернет-магазина.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.6.2]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[289.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[194.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/616235-pprod/advanced-pack-5.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/616235-pbig/advanced-pack-5.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1504]]></id><name><![CDATA[upstrackingv2]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[UPS Delivery Status]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Отслеживание заказа]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Including this mode of delivery is absolutely essential, for it offers your customers a speedy, tracked delivery]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/delivery-tracking/1504-ups-delivery-status.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1504.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Including this mode of delivery is absolutely essential, for it offers your customers a speedy, tracked delivery.﻿ No 1 package retailer in the Unites States, UPS is a key player in the world of e-commerce.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Take advantage of the UPS Tracking module: &nbsp;Get advanced tracking for your shipments, step by step, straight from your Back OfficeImprove your customers&rsquo; overall purchasing experience by regularly informing them about their order status and delivery of their package&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/611439-pprod/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/611439-pbig/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1615]]></id><name><![CDATA[gshopping]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Shopping (Merchant Center)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Сравнение цен]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[ Простой экспорт вашего каталога в Google Shopping: новая услуга сравнивая цен, разработанная Google! Внимание: Для заказа этого модуля необходимо обратиться к компании-партнеру]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/price-comparison/1615-google-shopping-merchant-center.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1615.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[ Простой экспорт вашего каталога в Google Shopping: новая услуга сравнивая цен, разработанная Google! Внимание: Для заказа этого модуля необходимо обратиться к компании-партнеру. Перед покупкой данного модуля просьба подписаться на эту услугу этой компании.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase visits to your shop&nbsp; 80 million product searches in Google! When you register your products, all users will be able to find them when they search with Google and buy them directly from your online shop. You can also find new customers using Google Shopping apps for tablets and mobile devices. &nbsp;Save time&nbsp; Our module allows you to export your products to Google Shopping as simply as possible. Quick, intuitive, easy-to-use interface. &nbsp;Increase your conversion rate using Google qualified traffic&nbsp; Visitors arriving from Google Shopping have selected your product from the images available... so they are ready to buy. &nbsp;Improve the positioning of your shop on the search engine by using Google tools&nbsp;Increase your international visibility.&nbsp; You can export your catalogue in various currencies to publicise your products to consumers in all the countries where Google Shopping is present. &nbsp;Google Shopping is one of the marketplaces with best return on investment.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[129.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[149.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[104.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/708922-pprod/google-shopping-merchant-center.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/708922-pbig/google-shopping-merchant-center.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2376]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestagiftvouchers]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Coupons / Discount vouchers]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Обеспечения лояльности покупателей и акций "Приведи друга"]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[    ]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/referral-loyalty-programs/2376-coupons-discount-vouchers.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2376.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[    ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the Loyalty&nbsp;Discount Vouchers module you can:  &nbsp;Automatically create cart rules that generate offer codes emailed to your customers,&nbsp;Customize the coupons&rsquo; name, their value as a percentage or amount as well as their validity period,&nbsp;Increase average cart size on your site by defining minimum purchase amounts in order to use the discount voucher,&nbsp;Build customer loyalty by encouraging customers to buy again from your store,&nbsp;Easily liquidate your inventory of products of your choice, and better promote your new products and categories]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[49.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/708607-pprod/coupons-discount-vouchers.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/708607-pbig/coupons-discount-vouchers.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2501]]></id><name><![CDATA[amazon]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Market Place]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Торговая площадка]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/marketplaces/2501-amazon-market-place.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2501.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[You can easily integrate your PrestaShop store to the world&rsquo;s top marketplace and significantly increase your sales. You import your orders into your PrestaShop store and centralize your stocks.  Managing your inventory efficiently and quickly honoring your Amazon orders allows you to increase the degree of customer satisfaction and thus automatically increase the rank of your seller performance.  The design of the module is based on the initial experience of online retailers. The module was developed by an online retailer for the service of his colleagues and it was developed by a team of professional developers, by making it easy to use and to have the maximum efficiency.  Your purchase is protected by free technical support that is provided unconditionally until the products are placed online and the first orders are imported.  This module was developed by Common-Services, which is a partner agency of Prestashop. Common-Services has been featuring on PrestaShop Addons&nbsp; since 2010 and it has also published 15 other best-selling modules that are marketed only on PrestaShop Addons.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.266]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[224.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[154.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/686436-pprod/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/686436-pbig/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2778]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedsearch4]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Search 4]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Поиск и фильтры]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Best Module Award Winner -&nbsp;Add the fastest layered navigation system for PrestaShop !]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/search-filters/2778-advanced-search-4.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2778.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Best Module Award Winner -&nbsp;Add the fastest layered navigation system for PrestaShop !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Provide to your customers the products that meet their needs.  Indispensable tool for shops offering a wide selection of products,&nbsp;Advanced Search 4&nbsp;can add as many search engines as you want and place them in different places on your website. This module was developed in an effort to provide short loading times, even on large catalogs. Your visitors can browse products that match their search criteria, to make their purchases in minimal time.  Winner of the Best PrestaShop Modules Awards 2012  Advanced Search 4 won the&nbsp;Best module&nbsp;of the year Award at the PrestaShop BarCamp of Barcelona (Spain)!  Indispensable tool for shops offering a wide selection of products.  Advanced Search 4&nbsp;adds the multi-layered navigation, search by step, filters and multi-criteria searches. Each search is saved over the navigation, allowing your visitors to return to the results of their research at any time.  Google is his friend  This PrestaShop Addon is a small revolution for SEO. Advanced Search 4 generate a mass-produced products pages optimized for SEO, and without duplicate content! Pick up your criteria on which you want to improve your SEO, validate them, and here you go with hundreds of pages listing your products, including: re-written URL, H1 tags, description, meta tags, automatised cross links...&nbsp;  To maximize your reputation, these results pages can be shared on most social networks places around the internet, as well as sent by e-mail.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[search_filter]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.11.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[229.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[159.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573189-pprod/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573189-pbig/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2792]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmuassocprodcat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Association flash Products / Categories]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Быстрое & массовое редактирование]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/mass-updates/2792-dmu-association-flash-products-categories.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2792.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time! In one interface, all in ajax (without reloading the page), see the products associated to a category. Look for products that you want to add to this category and add them in one click! You also can control the default category of your products directly through the icon on the right.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/741974-pprod/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/741974-pbig/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2937]]></id><name><![CDATA[storemanager]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[STORE MANAGER]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Инструменты администрирования]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[30-ДНЕВНАЯ БЕСПЛАТНАЯ ВЕРСИЯ! Решение для администраторов онлайн магазина которое Вы должны попробовать! Store Manager for PrestaShop дает возможность выполнять большинство операций по управлению инте]]></description><author><![CDATA[eMagicOne]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/administration-tools/2937-store-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2937.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[30-ДНЕВНАЯ БЕСПЛАТНАЯ ВЕРСИЯ! Решение для администраторов онлайн магазина которое Вы должны попробовать! Store Manager for PrestaShop дает возможность выполнять большинство операций по управлению интернет магазином на базе PrestaShop в два раза быстрее, делая работу более простой и удобной.   Store Manager for PrestaShop это программа для настольного компьютера или ноутбука работающего под OS Windows специально созданная для ускорения и автоматизации работы администратора онлайн магазина на базе PrestaShop. Store Manager не только делает более удобным выполнение массовых операций с продуктами, категориями, заказами и клиентами расширяя функциональность стандартной панели администрирования но также привносит новый функционал реализованый в дополнениях таких как QuickBooks Integration, Peachtree Integration, USPS Integratrion, POS, Automated Product Import и других.   ﻿﻿*** ПОБЕДИТЕЛЬ В НОМИНАЦИИ “ЛУЧШИЙ МОДУЛЬ” ЦЕРЕМОНИИ PRESTASHOP AWARDS﻿ ***    ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Экономьте время, деньги и ресурсы, позвольте Store Manager’у делать рутинную работу вместо Вас. Store Manager поможет Вашему магазину выделиться из толпы!  Потратьте час, сэкономьте день! Store Manager for PrestaShop был создан  чтобы работать на Вас. Это Ваш персональный ассистент который выполняет большинство рутинных задач экономя Вам время для более приятных дел. Импорт и экспорт, отчеты, дополнения - не нужно тратить дни разбираясь в деталях работы магазна, потратьте несколько часов чтобы научиться работать со Store Manager’ом.  Приобретайте один Store Manager for PrestaShop вместо целой кучи модулей. Используйте один продукт для управления несколькими магазинами. Store Manager не требует особых навыков и знаний, Вам не нужно платить кому-то для поддержания вашего магазина в актуальном стостоянии. Большинство важных операций можно выполнить быстро и смостоятельно.  Попробуйте 30-дневную ознакомительную версию! Вы уже пользуетесь Store Manager’ом? Оставьте свой отзыв!﻿﻿]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/689783-pprod/store-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/689783-pbig/store-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3252]]></id><name><![CDATA[printlabels]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Print Labels Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Подготовка и отправка]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Save valuable time by automating the publishing of your shipping labels! This module for PrestaShop lets you edit and print shipping labels to stick on your package, based on orders placed on your sit]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/preparation-shipping/3252-print-labels.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3252.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Save valuable time by automating the publishing of your shipping labels! This module for PrestaShop lets you edit and print shipping labels to stick on your package, based on orders placed on your site.﻿]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time shipping your ordersLower your rate of returned packages due to wrong addresses]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595260-pprod/print-labels.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595260-pbig/print-labels.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3438]]></id><name><![CDATA[auctions]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Auctions]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Создать сайт аукционов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Auctions module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/build-auction-site/3438-auctions.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3438.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Auctions module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way. With a number of great features and intuitive interface, this is the best auctions module available for Prestashop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way. Auctions are the great way to attract and keep customers in your shop. You will be sure that customer is paying right price for your products. You don't have to negotiate prices with customers anymore. Managing auctions is very intuitive, and fully integrated with your shop. You will feel like it's not a module but integral part of the PrestaShop.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[29.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/625145-pprod/auctions.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/625145-pbig/auctions.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4414]]></id><name><![CDATA[allinone_rewards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[All-in-one Rewards: loyalty sponsorship affiliation FB]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Обеспечения лояльности покупателей и акций "Приведи друга"]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, fa]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/referral-loyalty-programs/4414-all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4414.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, facebook and more. Your sales will really increase !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get tons of new customers and increase your brand reputation thanks to the All-in-one Rewards module !  This module allows to set up a complete system of rewards in your shop to increase SEO and reputation thanks to the virality of the system, and to follow very precisely the performance.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[224.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[154.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/617761-pprod/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/617761-pbig/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4982]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_seointernallinking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Internal Linking]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Естественная поисковая оптимизация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/4982-seo-internal-linking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4982.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Enhance your PrestaShop SEO  Internal linking&nbsp;is the creation of links between pages of your shop, using keywords you want to achieve a&nbsp;better place on Google.  To&nbsp;optimize the SEO of your website, it is essential to create an&nbsp;internal linking&nbsp;that will allow search engines to browse your shop in the most easy way as possible. The goal is to provide maximum informations with the least clicks deep.  SEO Internal Linking&nbsp;PrestaShop module optimizes the organization of navigation in your store, and plays an essential role in your&nbsp;SEO strategy.  Define the keywords on which you wish to be listed and their landing pages, and let the module create the links for you!  If you want to add automatic links in your categories descriptions, consider installing our PrestaShop module&nbsp;HTML On Descriptions.  Do we really need internal linking?  Internal linking strategy&nbsp;based on specific keywords is an optimization method that has proven its worth. Especially to enhance a content relevance.  Among the disadvantages, you should know that the installation of these links is long and tedious, and requires to&nbsp;follow SEO good practices, to not over-optimize (which would be detected by Google), and must be updated regularly to track changes in your catalog.  With this in mind, we have developed this module, allowing you to deploy thousands of cross links between your pages within minutes, while being sure to observe best practice guidelines of White Hat SEO.  It has been designed to support both SEO agencies and e-shop owners. SEO Internal Linking&nbsp;is really simple to manage.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.11]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.3.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[119.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pprod/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pbig/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5255]]></id><name><![CDATA[ordertaxprofitreport]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Статистика и анализ]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/analytics-statistics/5255-advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5255.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get perfect visibility on your shop's and products' profitability !  The default PrestaShop installation does not provide a one-click tool that allows you to obtain important accounting and financial data: tax due, net sales volume after discounts and, most importantly, profit and profit margin.  Not only will this report provide you with all this data, but it will even allow you to answer questions like "what percentage of total sales and / or profits does this specific brand, supplier or product category represent ?".  This stylish and pleasant AJAX based module allows you to generate different types of preformed reports with all this information. They can be viewed on screen in HTML format or exported as a CSV file to manipulate in Excel and / or import into any other information or accounting system.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011 PrestaShop Awards for Best module.    You are guaranteed to buy a quality module and to get fast and efficient tech support in case you need it.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.9.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.3.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[119.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/764303-pprod/advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/764303-pbig/advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6059]]></id><name><![CDATA[cdiscount]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cdiscount Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Торговая площадка]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/marketplaces/6059-cdiscount-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6059.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders. Beneficiate from 3-month subscription free when you register on Cdiscount !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[C Le March&eacute; is one of France&rsquo;s leading marketplaces.  Boost your sales! Make the most of the traffic generated by Cdiscount to sell your products and enjoy the numerous advantages which make Cdiscount such a success: - payment in 4 instalments (fully supported by Cdiscount) - multiple delivery methods, etc.  Cdiscount takes care of everything! Place your products for sale on the marketplace and manage your orders while Cdiscount takes care of the rest: traffic, easy and secure payment, marketing, etc.  1 single back office! Thanks to the Cdiscount for PrestaShop module, you no longer need to manage several different back offices. In just a few clicks, connect your PrestaShop site to your Cdiscount store and post your products: - Product descriptions are exported directly to the Cdiscount marketplace, - Prices and inventories are automatically updated, - Your orders will be directly imported and integrated into your PrestaShop store.  Practical and easy configuration! Once you have configured your module, exports are automatic meaning you no longer have any data to handle.  A module developed by an e-merchant for e-merchants! The module&rsquo;s design is based on the early experience of online retailers. It was created by an e-merchants&nbsp;for the benefit of fellow e-merchants&nbsp;and developed by a team of professional developers, resulting in maximum user friendliness and efficiency.  Free technical support! Your purchase is guaranteed by free technical support provided unconditionally until your products are placed online and your first orders are imported.   *This offer applies for merchants already registered on&nbsp;CleMarch&eacute;&nbsp;Marketplace and cannot be used in combination with&nbsp;any other ongoing&nbsp;Cdiscount.com&nbsp;offer.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.9.174]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[114.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/715585-pprod/cdiscount-marketplace.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/715585-pbig/cdiscount-marketplace.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6144]]></id><name><![CDATA[gsnippetsreviews]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Customer Ratings and Reviews Pro + Google Rich Snippets]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Естественная поисковая оптимизация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Conversion rate increase guaranteed: The most complete and powerful customer rating & review system, plus Google Rich Snippets functionality]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/6144-customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6144.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Conversion rate increase guaranteed: The most complete and powerful customer rating & review system, plus Google Rich Snippets functionality.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With Google Rich Snippets, benefit from visually enhanced results on Google's search engine results and increase your click rate, numbers visitors and sales ! The full rating and review system will also greatly improve your shop's conversion rate and further increase your sales.  If you have already purchased our Facebook PS Wall Posts module (sold separately on http://addons.prestashop.com/en/social-commerce-facebook-prestashop-modules/4429-Facebook-PS-Wall-Posts.html), you can have any rating / review automatically posted on your Facebook fan page.  This module is also fully compatible and integrates with Presta-Module's "Advanced Pack 5" module, available on http://addons.prestashop.com/en/merchandising-prestashop-modules/1015-advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.html  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011 & 2014 PrestaShop Awards for Best module.  You are guaranteed to buy a quality module and to get fast and efficient tech support in case you need it.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[114.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/705340-pprod/customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/705340-pbig/customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6291]]></id><name><![CDATA[siretcustomergroup]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SIRET and customer group]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Управления учетными записями клиентов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/customer-administration/6291-siret-and-customer-group.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6291.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Finally, you can easily manage your professional customers just by asking their SIRET to transfer them in a client group or there is no tax for example, with prices reduced (e.g. wholesalers)...]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/101289-pprod/siret-and-customer-group.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/101289-pbig/siret-and-customer-group.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6356]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_multiplefeatures]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Multiple Features - Assign your features as you want]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Поиск и фильтры]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Multiple Features allows you to assign multiple values ​​of features to your products]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/search-filters/6356-multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6356.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Multiple Features allows you to assign multiple values ​​of features to your products]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Add features to your PrestaShop catalog without limits!  With&nbsp;Multiple Features, you can assign as many values as necessary for the same product and the same feature. Remove this PrestaShop limitation and start using your features as you want!  If you also use our layered navigation system&nbsp;Advanced Search 4&nbsp;(Winner of PrestaShop Best Module Awards 2012), you can give to your customers a more relevant research in your catalog.  Customer study :  Ocarat.com: &quot;Some jewelry may have a different composition and an alloy of several metals. PrestaShop provides the ability to associate a feature to a product. However, I want to integrate in my shop a gold ring set with diamonds and emeralds. But features tab does not allow me to do so. I can&#39;t assign multiple values to a single purpose. So I have to choose between gold, diamonds or emeralds.&nbsp;Multiple Features remove PrestaShop limits and allows you to use features as you want !&quot;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[search_filter]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.9.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573403-pprod/multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/573403-pbig/multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6413]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_cachemanager]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cache Manager]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Повышения эффективности сайта]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Decrease your loading page time generation]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/website-performances/6413-cache-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6413.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Decrease your loading page time generation]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Improve your conversion rate and SEO  The statistics are clear: the main reason why a user leave a web page is the loading time.  Yahoo! said that adding 400ms to the page loading time on their car website raises the dropout rate from 5 to 9%. (Sources: Performance Web)  In addition, the speed display is a guarantee of quality which has a very positive influence on the positioning in the search engines.  Let your customers enjoy a more comfortable navigation on your website by shortening the loading time of pages, and saving his time!  Limited offer : Price drop &amp; Satisfied or refunded !]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.12]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[114.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573569-pprod/cache-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/573569-pbig/cache-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7152]]></id><name><![CDATA[customfields]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Custom Fields]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Registration & Ordering Process]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create unlimited number of custom fields for registration form. You can add all kinds of fields: text, text area, radio buttons, check boxes and select lists with unlimited number of options and more]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/registration-ordering-process/7152-custom-fields.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/7152.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create unlimited number of custom fields for registration form. You can add all kinds of fields: text, text area, radio buttons, check boxes and select lists with unlimited number of options and more.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[It's important to know about as much as possible about customers. It will help with better understanding of the clients habits and needs. That knowledge will allow e-merchant to improve it's services and finally make more profit of his business. Custom fields module in easy way allows you to create unlimited number of custom fields and get all required data about your customers that cannot be done with standard registration form. All fields can be validated with selected validation rule and can be viewed and editable in the backoffice.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/582276-pprod/custom-fields.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/582276-pbig/custom-fields.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7422]]></id><name><![CDATA[groupinc]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Price Increment/Reduction by group, category and more]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Управления учетными записями клиентов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Would you like to apply an Increment, Reduction or Fixed Price to your catalog product price?  With this module you can do it by Category, by Product, by Customer Group, by Customer, by Country, by Zo]]></description><author><![CDATA[Idnovate]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/customer-administration/7422-price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/7422.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Would you like to apply an Increment, Reduction or Fixed Price to your catalog product price?  With this module you can do it by Category, by Product, by Customer Group, by Customer, by Country, by Zone, by Supplier and by Manufacturer.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Apply a markup or offer a discount in your products Feel free to play with a markup in the price of your products creating an increment or a reduction configuration by category, by product, by customer group, by customer, by country, by zone, by supplier and by manufacturer.  Set a massive fixed price ★ ¡New! ★  You could set a massive fixed price to the products using the conditions by category, by product, by customer group, by customer, by country, by zone, by supplier and by manufacturer. Example of use: You can create a new category, associate the products to this category and with our module you could set all this category products to 20$ without changing the original product price and without creating complicated discount rules to obtain the desired price.  No multistore needed for the same catalog products The customers group filter allows to avoid creating a multistore for a B2B and B2C store, sharing the same catalog products but with different prices in each.  Forget the limitations, show to your customers the product prices which do you want to really show.  Our guarantees  ✪ We are a PrestaShop Partner agency. All our developers are certified by PrestaShop. ✔ We can customize the module or make any modifications that you may need. Contact us for a quote. Do you have any questions or concerns? Send us a message! We will happily answer any questions]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/732617-pprod/price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/732617-pbig/price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7484]]></id><name><![CDATA[newsletterpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Newsletter Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Рассылка новостей и SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module for PrestaShop allows you to create and send your own newsletters with different products from your store using many customizable templates]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/newsletter-sms/7484-newsletter-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/7484.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module for PrestaShop allows you to create and send your own newsletters with different products from your store using many customizable templates.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We all know that advertising plays a key role in promoting any business. Using our newsletter will boost your sales faster and easier than any other newsletter module available on the market. This module is an easy and fast way to send customizable newsletters about top selling products or special offers to your clients.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.4.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[94.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Traffic"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/awards-traffic.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/724699-pprod/newsletter-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/724699-pbig/newsletter-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8734]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgcookieslaw]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[EU Cookie Law (Notification Banner + Cookie Blocker)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Администрация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The only module that allows you to fully comply with the EU cookie law. Display a responsive and custom warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent]]></description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/legal/8734-eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8734.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The only module that allows you to fully comply with the EU cookie law. Display a responsive and custom warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our module fully complies with the European Cookie Law.  Complete compliance with the law  Besides displaying a warning banner, our module is the only one that allows you to block the cookies when users enter your store. As established by the law, you "shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information."  Please note that all the other cookie modules sold on Addons only allows you to display a warning banner regardless of the user consent. Cookies are installed on the users' computer without obtaining their consent and regardless of their will.  Main features of the modulesDisplay a warning banner on every page to inform users about the use of cookies and ask for their consentDisable a list of modules when users enter the website because warning users about cookies is useless and illegal if you have already installed cookies on their computer.Enable these cookies after having obtained their consent or maintain them disabled if they refuse.Fully customize the warning banner (color, text, link, font, position, multilingual mode, transparency, buttons...) Getting the user consent   The module includes 2 different ways to ask user consent, you can choose between:Acceptance through a button: Users must click on the "I accept" button in the warning banner to give his consent. As soon as users give their consent, the warning banner disappears and all the modules using cookies will get enabled and will work as usual. But if users refuse to give their consent, the disabled modules will remain disabled. We recommend you to use this mode, this one allows you to fully comply with the law.Acceptance through the navigation: If users continue browsing the website, they will accept the use of cookies. The warning banner is displayed on the first page on which users arrive with a message like « By continuing browsing the website, you accept the use of cookies ». As soon as users decide to go to another page, the banner automatically disappears and the disabled modules will get enabled.Note: the consent remains valid during the period of time set in the module interface (we recommend you not to go over 13 months)  Customizing the banner content and design  As recommended by the European authority, the module allows you to customize the warning message inside the banner (to inform users about the cookies users and their purpose) and add a "More information" button into the banner that take users to a CMS page of your store (to explain in details the use of cookies on your store).  The warning banner is responsive and will always be displayed full-width. The module comes with a Wysiwyg editor that allows you to fully customize the content of the banner (font, color, effects, html code, links...). You can also choose from the configuration page the background color of the banner, its percentage of opacity (transparency) and its position (top or bottom of the page). Moreover, the module is multilingual and automatically detects all the languages of your store, which allows you to set a different warning message per language.  Note: the module is designed to not display a warning message when search engines robots crawl you store in order not to affect your SEO.  Disabling the modules that use cookies  This is the only module that allows you to choose the modules/cookies that you want to disable until users give their consent. This feature is compulsory because it is useless and illegal to inform users if you have already installed cookies on their computer with their consent.  "Member States shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information, in accordance with Directive 95/46/EC” EU Cookie Law  To comply with the directive of the EU Cookie Law, we recommend you to disable the tracking (Google Analytics), social sharing (Facebook " Like ", Google " +1 ", etc.) and targeted advertising modules. Please note that all modules that are required for the good running of your PrestaShop store (ex: basket cookie, session cookie...) don't require any consents.  Multistore mode  The module is compatible with multistore and allows you to display the same notification banner on each one of your shop but the consent is the same for all shops. If you accept the use of cookies on one of your shop, the module will consider that you accept the use of cookies for all your other shops (mention it on your cookie policy) and the notification banner will not be shown when you go to your other shops.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[25.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689395-pprod/eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689395-pbig/eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8741]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmulistecommandes]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Improved Order List]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Управление заказами]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Save time on the processing of your orders! Avoid having to enter each order one after the other to get all the details. This module lets you know everything from your order list]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/order-management/8741-dmu-improved-order-list.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8741.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Save time on the processing of your orders! Avoid having to enter each order one after the other to get all the details. This module lets you know everything from your order list.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The more orders you have to process, the more this module will save you time. As much by the fact that all information is available from the order list and because you will be able to change status in mass with this module.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/740079-pprod/dmu-improved-order-list.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/740079-pbig/dmu-improved-order-list.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[11345]]></id><name><![CDATA[pushoncart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Push on Cart]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Перекрестные продажи и Создание комплектов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Мы приглашаем вас быстро увеличить средне-покупательную способность корзины ваших клиентов, благодаря специальной акции прекрасно адаптированной для покупательной способности ваших клиентов]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/cross-selling-product-bundles/11345-push-on-cart.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/11345.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Мы приглашаем вас быстро увеличить средне-покупательную способность корзины ваших клиентов, благодаря специальной акции прекрасно адаптированной для покупательной способности ваших клиентов.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[свободное повышение средне-покупательной способности корзины ваших клиентов легкое сбывание запасов продуктов по вашему выбору дайте попробовать вашим клиентам те новые продукты, которые они может еще не знают, создавая потребность, и верность покупателя повышение удовлетворенности клиентов через акции приятно адаптированные к их потребностям]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.3.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595049-pprod/push-on-cart.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595049-pbig/push-on-cart.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[13654]]></id><name><![CDATA[hspointofsalepro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[RockPOS Point of Sale (POS) Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Кассовое ПО]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Thanks to RockPOS (formerly Point of Sale Pro), now you can sell your products online and offline as well, at your stores / warehouses, exhibitions, trade conferences or via phone / chat]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/point-of-sale-pos/13654-rockpos-point-of-sale-pos-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/13654.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Thanks to RockPOS (formerly Point of Sale Pro), now you can sell your products online and offline as well, at your stores / warehouses, exhibitions, trade conferences or via phone / chat. All transactions are connected to your cloud database.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Sell your products anywhere, anytime in secondsCentralize your data, no need extra time to combine your manual orders]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.4.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[114.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/618511-pprod/rockpos-point-of-sale-pos-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/618511-pbig/rockpos-point-of-sale-pos-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16939]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoexpert]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Expert]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Естественная поисковая оптимизация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase site traffic by landing on first page search engine results!  This SEO Expert module automatically fills in both meta tags and social media meta tags to optimize your online store for better ]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/16939-seo-expert.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/16939.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase site traffic by landing on first page search engine results!  This SEO Expert module automatically fills in both meta tags and social media meta tags to optimize your online store for better visibility on search engines and social media platforms.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Automatically create meta tags to save over 40 hours! With the SEO Expert module:Appear on first page results on search engines like Google, Bing, Yahoo, Yandex, etc.Multiply your sales with increased web trafficImprove visibility for each language of your storeIncrease your conversions with qualified trafficDifferentiate your store with fully customized rules for product and category pagesLeverage Facebook and Twitter to acquire even more customersOptimize your online store for social media with adapted shared titles]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.17]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[119.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595316-pprod/seo-expert.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595316-pbig/seo-expert.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17452]]></id><name><![CDATA[giftcards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Gift Card]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Список желаний и Подарочный купон]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase your sales and get more customers by offering them the chance to give the perfect gift with no risks with the Gift Card module developed by PrestaShop!&nbsp;Practical and simple, gift cards a]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/wishlist-gift-card/17452-gift-card.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/17452.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase your sales and get more customers by offering them the chance to give the perfect gift with no risks with the Gift Card module developed by PrestaShop!&nbsp;Practical and simple, gift cards are at the top of the list of the most given gifts!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This solution provides the possibility of offering gift cards for any amount you like in your store.&nbsp;Every customer can buy your gift cards to offer people the chance to come and spend them in your store.&nbsp;&nbsp;This module allows you to:&nbsp;Pick up new customers: gift card beneficiaries represent a market of new prospects you can&rsquo;t pass up!&nbsp;Increase your sales: gift card beneficiaries often spend more than the amount bought on the card.&nbsp;Encourage indecisive customers to buy: if you offer a simple gift, suitable for all targets, customers won&rsquo;t hesitate.&nbsp;&nbsp;The gift card market brings great success with consumers and its annual growth varies between 20% and 40%.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[104.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[69.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/597595-pprod/gift-card.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/597595-pbig/gift-card.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17497]]></id><name><![CDATA[netreviews]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Verified Reviews]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Отзывы клиентов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Website and product reviews from your clients can increase your sales ! Collect them now with Verified Reviews and get your adwords stars thanks to our partnership with Google]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/customer-reviews/17497-netreviews.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/17497.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Website and product reviews from your clients can increase your sales ! Collect them now with Verified Reviews and get your adwords stars thanks to our partnership with Google.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Collect and publish reviews from your clients with the trusted third-party Verified Reviews.&nbsp; &nbsp; Why choose us ?&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; With Verified Reviews, you can now enjoy :&nbsp; &nbsp; - A full tailor-made solution&nbsp; &nbsp; - Packages including the collect of both website and product reviews&nbsp; &nbsp; - Unbeatable prices-The best feedback rate of the market&nbsp; &nbsp; - Great facebook applications - A certificate of authenticity&nbsp; &nbsp; - Stars in Adwords thanks to our partnership with Google&nbsp; &nbsp; - An offer WITHOUT OBLIGATION&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[7.1.41]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/603426-pprod/netreviews.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/603426-pbig/netreviews.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18016]]></id><name><![CDATA[supercheckout]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Knowband - One Page Checkout, Social Login & Mailchimp]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Процесс заказа]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Mobile responsive One Page Checkout with Facebook/Google+, MAILCHIMP and Ship2Pay. It can be used with any theme & any payment method]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/express-checkout-process/18016-knowband-one-page-checkout-social-login-mailchimp.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/18016.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Mobile responsive One Page Checkout with Facebook/Google+, MAILCHIMP and Ship2Pay. It can be used with any theme & any payment method.  It is also compatible with Mondial Relay like shipping methods which shows iframe or popup on selection.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Show/Hide any Fields: Decide which fields you want to display on our one page checkout module. Module has the functionality to show/hide fields like Company, VAT, Address title etc.  Customize buttons: Change our page buttons color to match them with your theme template by using color picker tool of our module admin panel. No coding knowledge is required.  Mailchimp: Send Customer email id directly to Mailchimp either when customer come out from email field or when he place order after selecting checkbox for newsletter subscription. If some customer logins via Google or Facebook button, even then his email will be sent to Mailchimp.  Change Shipping/Payment method name or image: Our checkout module allows admin to change shipping/payment methods name or image easily without any change in the code.  Make any field optional: There is an option using which admin can make any field optional or mandatory.  Sort address fields: Admin can also manage sorting of all address fields using drag and drop feature. Example: Phone number field can be placed just before First name etc.  Drag and Drop: Change position of all blocks using drag and drop features. You can also show payment method first and shipping method below.  Language Translation: Module also has the functionality to translate the module text in any language from admin panel.  Ship2pay: Using this feature admin can disable payment methods based upon customer shipping method selection.  Custom CSS and JS: There is an option in admin panel to add custom CSS and JS. Admin can use this feature to make desired changes without editing core files of module.  Custom HTML: This one page checkout module also has an option to add multiple custom HTML block at any place. Admin can promote any product, display any promotion OR provide any messages to our customers regarding deal, shipping or payment method information etc.  Testing mode: Module has a testing mode using which admins can test our module on their live site without affecting their ongoing business. If testing mode is enabled, all customers will go to default checkout of Prestashop and admin can test our module page using a URL which will be shown in our module's admin side.  FAQ tab: We understand value of your time and therefore we have added all basic queries related to our module in our admin panel so that you don't need to contact us for small issues/queries.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[94.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/749617-pprod/knowband-one-page-checkout-social-login-mailchimp.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/749617-pbig/knowband-one-page-checkout-social-login-mailchimp.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18850]]></id><name><![CDATA[orderedit]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Order Edit - Edit existing order]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Управление заказами]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With this module you ca modify and alter every existing order in your store, also after the purchase is completed]]></description><author><![CDATA[Silbersaiten]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/order-management/18850-order-edit-edit-existing-order.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/18850.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With this module you ca modify and alter every existing order in your store, also after the purchase is completed. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Articles information, shipping information, payments and discounts can be modified. Please refer to the screens, the video, the demoshop, or contact us directly in order to get more information on how the module works. &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[49.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/644053-pprod/order-edit-edit-existing-order.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/644053-pbig/order-edit-edit-existing-order.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18921]]></id><name><![CDATA[mailchimp]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Mailchimp Newsletter 1.6]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Рассылка новостей и SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Manage your newsletters easily with this module allowing you to create, send and monitor customized newsletter campaigns from the PrestaShop back office]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/newsletter-sms/18921-official-mailchimp-for-prestashop-16.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/18921.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Manage your newsletters easily with this module allowing you to create, send and monitor customized newsletter campaigns from the PrestaShop back office.  Thanks to Mailchimp,&nbsp;send up to 12,000 e-mails a month for free !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With official Mailchimp for PrestaShop, you can:Create entirely personalised newsletters.Add product images to your newsletters in 1 clic and schedule them easily.Promote customer loyalty by importing your Mailchimp customer lists and updating your customers with your special offers and latest news of your store.Update your customer lists at any time with the new ones registered with your store.Maximise reading and opening rates thanks to customer segmentation (mailings to customers who have opened or clicked on a previous newsletter, etc.).Monitor your campaigns using full reports included directly in your PrestaShop back office.Benefit from the Mailchimp free plan which allows you to send 12,000 emails per month and have 2,000 suscribers for free ! &nbsp; Mailchimp is already used by more than 7 million customers, now it is your turn!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[129.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[144.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[99.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/645020-pprod/official-mailchimp-for-prestashop-16.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/645020-pbig/official-mailchimp-for-prestashop-16.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19554]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestastripe]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Official Stripe for PrestaShop]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Оплата банковской картой или с помощью электронного кошелька]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Accept credit and debit card payments on your store from your customers all over the world thanks to PrestaShop&rsquo;s Stripe payment module!  This clear and optimized payment solution lets you insta]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/payment-card-wallet/19554-official-stripe-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19554.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Accept credit and debit card payments on your store from your customers all over the world thanks to PrestaShop&rsquo;s Stripe payment module!  This clear and optimized payment solution lets you instantly accept credit and debit card transactions directly from your back office, all the while ensuring top-level security.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Improve your conversion rate by accepting simple, fast credit and debit card payments directly on your storeEasily configure the Stripe module on your online storeYou can make refunds directly from your store&rsquo;s back officeBoost your international sales by accepting payments in several currenciesSimple, fair pricing adapted based on your revenue (no monthly or hidden fees and no refund costs)]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[114.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/667929-pprod/official-stripe-for-prestashop.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/667929-pbig/official-stripe-for-prestashop.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19927]]></id><name><![CDATA[quotation]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Online Quotation]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Расчет цены]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allow customers to ask for a quote in your online shop! With the Online quotation module, create a made-to-measure form so your customers can ask for an estimate for the products they are interested i]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/quotes/19927-online-quotation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19927.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allow customers to ask for a quote in your online shop! With the Online quotation module, create a made-to-measure form so your customers can ask for an estimate for the products they are interested in and you pick up all the information you needed to create an estimate.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase the conversion rate of your shop by making an attractive offer by estimateIncrease the average shopping cart by encouraging your customers to buy more products they hadn&rsquo;t planned toAllow your customers to order items they are interested in&nbsp;using offers by estimateOptimise your shop&rsquo;s reassurance and customer satisfaction by advising your customers using estimates&nbsp; Make a personalised study and follow-up of every estimate request you receive. Send your proposal to your customer, who can turn the estimate into an order with a single click. &nbsp; Our tip: A few days after sending the estimate, send a reminder e-mail using the &ldquo;Abandoned Cart Reminder Pro&rdquo; module&nbsp; &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.21]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[114.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/676340-pprod/online-quotation.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/676340-pbig/online-quotation.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20541]]></id><name><![CDATA[djtalbrazilianregister]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Brazilian Registration]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Registration & Ordering Process]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module adds the optional or obligatory fields of CPF, CNPJ, IE and RG in the registration form of your online store]]></description><author><![CDATA[BM Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/registration-ordering-process/20541-brazilian-registration.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20541.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module adds the optional or obligatory fields of CPF, CNPJ, IE and RG in the registration form of your online store. It also searches and fills the client&rsquo;s address with the CEP number and has a mask for the Brazilian phone number pattern.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The storeowner has total control over the requested information in the registration form. CPF and CNPJ &nbsp;can be configured as obligatory fields. The module will verify if the informed CPF or the CNPJ are correct. This information should be trustworthy for the issue of the Brazilian Nota Fiscal. The CEP can be used to obtain the client&rsquo;s address. For clients that don&rsquo;t know their CEP there is an option for the storeowner to display a &ldquo;I don&rsquo;t know my CEP&rdquo; button. This will redirect the customer to Correios website to get help.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[25.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/704295-pprod/brazilian-registration.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/704295-pbig/brazilian-registration.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20656]]></id><name><![CDATA[inmotion]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Inmotion]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Руководство]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[InMotion Hosting — это профессиональный поставщик услуг веб-хостинга, который предоставляет полностью масштабируемое решение, удовлетворяющее любые ваши потребности, связанные с сайтом]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/training/20656-inmotion.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20656.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[InMotion Hosting — это профессиональный поставщик услуг веб-хостинга, который предоставляет полностью масштабируемое решение, удовлетворяющее любые ваши потребности, связанные с сайтом. Обеспечивая круглосуточную поддержку для клиентов на территории США 7 дней в неделю и автоматическую установку PrestaShop, компания InMotion предоставляет решения общего, VPS- и выделенного хостинга. Сертификация CNET 3 звезды и рейтинг A+ Бюро по улучшению деловой практики.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Специалистам InMotion Hosting нравится PrestaShop! Мы предоставляем профессиональные услуги веб-размещения с 2001 г., предлагая решения общего, VPS- и выделенного хостинга, а также решения коммерческого класса практически для любого применения. Компания InMotion Hosting предоставляет специальный образовательный центр PrestaShop, содержащий множество руководств и статей, посвященных PrestaShop, и направленный на предоставление пользователям единого ресурса для установки и настройки как PrestaShop, так и нашей платформы хостинга. Сотрудники нашей службы технической поддержки прошли профессиональной обучение, чтобы надлежащим образом отвечать и реагировать на любые вопросы и проблемы, связанные с PrestaShop. Компания InMotion Hosting получает звание сертифицированного поставщика услуг хостинга с 3 звездами, начиная с 2003 г., и имеет рейтинг A+ Бюро по улучшению деловой практики. В качестве рекомендуемого поставщика услуг хостинга PrestaShop мы предлагаем установку в один щелчок посредством Softaculous. Продавцы  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[20659]]></id><name><![CDATA[webhostinghub]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[WebHostingHub]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Руководство]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Решение WebHostingHub — это самый простой способ получения доступа к вашему веб-сайту и выхода на рынок электронной коммерции, стоимость которого составляет лишь долю от той цены, которую запрашивают ]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/training/20659-webhostinghub.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20659.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Решение WebHostingHub — это самый простой способ получения доступа к вашему веб-сайту и выхода на рынок электронной коммерции, стоимость которого составляет лишь долю от той цены, которую запрашивают другие поставщики. Мы предоставляем нашим клиентам в США круглосуточную поддержку 7 дней в неделю без перерывов и выходных, неограниченные ресурсы и возможность установки PrestaShop в один щелчок; поэтому решение WebHostingHub позволит вам начать работать в течение нескольких минут!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Если вы только начинаете создавать веб-страницы или уже являетесь опытным веб-мастером, WebHostingHub предоставляет оптимальный вариант для всех. Благодаря наличию большого количества инструментов и ресурсов, а также круглосуточной поддержке 7 дней в неделю клиентов в США решение WebHostingHub позволит вам быстро и эффективно запустить ваш сайт без долгих и трудных часов программирования и кодирования.  Кроме того, мы предоставляем полноценный образовательный канал, где можно найти доступные для всех справочные руководства и ресурсы по PrestaShop.  Узнайте прямо сейчас, почему WebHostingHub является одним из лучших доступных решений по веб-хостингу. Мы подготовили специально для вас эксклюзивное предложение по PrestaShop.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[20844]]></id><name><![CDATA[productlabel]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Label]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Бейджи и Логотипы]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Customize your site and make your products more visible and more attractive, by displaying aesthetically pleasing customized labels on the images for the items of your choice!   The Product Label by P]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/labels-stickers/20844-product-label.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/20844.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Customize your site and make your products more visible and more attractive, by displaying aesthetically pleasing customized labels on the images for the items of your choice!   The Product Label by PrestaShop module is ideal for attracting the attention of your customers during sales, and helping them easily recognize your products on sale, your new products, and the best-sellers from your catalog.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Adapt your message and the icons of your labels according to the type of sales promotion you want.&nbsp;Tell your customers about special features and sales on your products, new items, and more :&nbsp;1 for 2, Free Shipping, Offer of the month, Last items left...&nbsp;Promote your products more and attract more attention from your customers with aesthetically pleasing icons and labels.&nbsp;Regularly refresh your site without changing your product catalog.&nbsp;Easily improve your conversion rate with display labels that encourage purchases.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/715640-pprod/product-label.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/715640-pbig/product-label.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21273]]></id><name><![CDATA[pqeasypost]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy Post Pro (DHL, UPS, Colis Privé, Royal Mail, etc.)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Подготовка и отправка]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to significaly increase the speed of your shipping process by integrating EasyPost]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/preparation-shipping/21273-easy-post-pro-dhl-ups-colis-prive-royal-mail-etc.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/21273.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to significaly increase the speed of your shipping process by integrating EasyPost.com API (Application Programming Interface) into PrestaShop and printing your shipping labels fast and easy. Only 3 cents per label!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We all know that in order to run a successful business you have to optimize it and automatize it as much as possible, this module allows you to do that by increasing the shipping process by 70%.   Think of how long it takes to receive an order from your customers, process the order by adding the products to the package, then connect to your shipping carrier`s software and manually insert the customer information, parcel information and delivery address for the order, for each order at a time. This is very time consuming and it`s very easy to make mistakes because you have a lot of data to process.  With this module all of this is done automatically via the API (Application Programming Interface) that connects the orders section in prestashop with the carrier and instantly sends the information to the carrier, then prints the shipping label which is then slicked to the package. The module supports the most important carriers in the world.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[114.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/726515-pprod/easy-post-pro-dhl-ups-colis-prive-royal-mail-etc.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/726515-pbig/easy-post-pro-dhl-ups-colis-prive-royal-mail-etc.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21278]]></id><name><![CDATA[popnewsletter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Popup Newsletter]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Всплывающие окна pop-in и pop-up]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The most effective way to stay in touch with your customers! Pop Newsletter creates a popup inviting your visitors to sign up for your newsletter]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/pop-in-pop-up/21278-pop-newsletter-popup.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/21278.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The most effective way to stay in touch with your customers! Pop Newsletter creates a popup inviting your visitors to sign up for your newsletter. With this professional and completely customisable pop-up, you can attract new subscribers and retain them with a discount on their next purchase.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Pop Newsletter allows you to show your visitors a pop-in when they arrive in your shop. Turn your visitors into subscribers! &nbsp; Improve the subscription rate for your shop:  Pop-ins are effective at attracting visitors&rsquo; attention, gaining more clicks than sliders, banners or sign-up panels in the footer (which have a conversion rate of only 0.05%). The proven results for this tool show increases of between 20% and 1,000% in your subscription rate. &nbsp; Turn your subscribers into loyal customers: Offer them a discount voucher for their next purchase in your shop to thank them for subscribing. &nbsp; Offer a flawless user experience: Similar to pop-ups but with an improved user experience, pop-ins integrate perfectly with the page where they appear. Pop Newsletter applies best practices recommended for this advertising method:Lightbox effectOption to close the module window with a simple click outside the pop-in, as well as a cross symbol button for closure in the top right-hand corner.Option to specify when the pop-in is activated. This allows your visitor to get to know your site before seeing the pop-in.Once your visitor closes the pop-in, it will not be shown again.Adaptable to all types of shop, with no need for programming or graphic design skills.&nbsp; &nbsp; Improve results from your newsletters by increasing your contact base: Thanks to the optional newsletter sign-up form, you can analyse and classify your subscribers more effectively. Pop Newsletter also allows you to send a confirmation e-mail to the e-mail address provided by your subscriber to ensure there is no chance of your newsletter being sent to an incorrect address.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/722395-pprod/pop-newsletter-popup.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/722395-pbig/pop-newsletter-popup.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21860]]></id><name><![CDATA[adyen]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Adyen Payment]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Оплата банковской картой или с помощью электронного кошелька]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Accept online payments anywhere in the world and expand your sales internationally thanks to an all-in-one payment solution by Adyen, a leader in international payment technologies]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/payment-card-wallet/21860-adyen-payment.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/21860.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Accept online payments anywhere in the world and expand your sales internationally thanks to an all-in-one payment solution by Adyen, a leader in international payment technologies.  &nbsp; Nothing is simpler to accept payments in your store: using this module, your customers are redirected to the Adyen payment page, reliable, secured, and customized according to your needs, to finalize their purchases.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Benefit from Adyen&#39;s local payment expertise covering the majority of developed and emerging e-commerce markets, and in doing so open yourself up more easily to the world.&nbsp;By accepting the majority of local and international payment methods in most payment currencies at your store, you will gain easy access to new segments of consumers and increase your income&nbsp;Adapt the solution to your needs and customize your payment page with your store&#39;s colour scheme and logo&nbsp;Benefit from Adyen&#39;s continuing innovation to gain maximum control, flexibility and adaptability to different local payment preferences.&nbsp;Optimize your conversion rate and reduce your costs thanks to this ready-to-use solution]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[229.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[159.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/733505-pprod/adyen-payment.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/733505-pbig/adyen-payment.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22098]]></id><name><![CDATA[jet]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Jet Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Торговая площадка]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Succeed your Jet]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/marketplaces/22098-jet-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/22098.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Succeed your Jet.com marketplace intergration and sell easily on the marketplace !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the Jet Marketplace for Prestashop module, your processing is automated, the products are exported directly to the Jet.com marketplace and your orders are automatically imported and integrated into your Prestashop store.  You also automate communication with your customers: your order confirmations are sent directly to the customer by email via the Jet.com web service, customers are automatically notified and the status of your orders is automatically updated.  By using the Jet Marketplace module, you maintain control of your offer and product flows, you automatically import your orders without additional cost or subscription and your data exchanges are automated and free.  Integration is easy and convenient: you configure your module, your export becomes automatic and so you have no more data to manipulate  Implementing scheduled tasks is simple and automated thanks to compatibility with the Prestashop Cron task-scheduling editor module (free). Just click on a button to automatically integrate your scheduled tasks in the module. It is still possible to manually configure your tasks.  The module design is based on the online merchant experience. The module was conceived by an online merchant in the service of his colleagues and developed by professional developers, which gives it ease of use and maximum effectiveness.  Your purchase is protected by free technical support which is assured unconditionally up to the moment of making the products available online and the import of your first orders.  The module provides a simplified configuration, native scheduled tasks, intelligent mapping, sleek design and good ergonomics.  This module was developed by Common-Services, which is a partner agency of Prestashop. Common-Services has been featuring on PrestaShop Addons since 2010 and it has also published more than 15 other best-selling modules that are marketed only on PrestaShop Addons.   You must have contracted with Jet.com prior to purchasing this module.  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.03]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[179.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[139.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/740793-pprod/jet-marketplace.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/740793-pbig/jet-marketplace.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22165]]></id><name><![CDATA[productslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Slider]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Слайдеров (карусельных) и галерей]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With PrestaShop&#39;s Product Slider, invest in an elegant, clear and simple presentation for your product visuals!   In e-commerce, seeing has replaced touching]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/sliders-galleries/22165-product-slider.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/22165.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With PrestaShop&#39;s Product Slider, invest in an elegant, clear and simple presentation for your product visuals!   In e-commerce, seeing has replaced touching. So create real visual impact on your site by presenting all your product photos in a sleek and attractive slider for easier conversions.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Create a strong visual impact and make your site more modern and attractiveHighlight your visuals on your product pages and improve their presentation to encourage your customers to look at all of the images available for each productAnd in doing so increase your product conversion rate&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/742057-pprod/product-slider.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/742057-pbig/product-slider.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22453]]></id><name><![CDATA[fastbay1]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[FastBay - eBay Marketplace synchronization]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Торговая площадка]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[FASTBAY&nbsp;is the professional solution to&nbsp;synchronize your Prestashop store with your Ebay account in few minutes &nbsp;]]></description><author><![CDATA[Prestalia]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/marketplaces/22453-fastbay-ebay-marketplace-synchronization.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/22453.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[FASTBAY&nbsp;is the professional solution to&nbsp;synchronize your Prestashop store with your Ebay account in few minutes &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Over&nbsp;1,250,000 Ebay Listings&nbsp;have been&nbsp;already created with FastBay.  EASY - A simplified configuration wizard will allow you to customize all settings without any problem in order to synchronize and manage products and orders. RELIABLE - Our module will assist you in every step of sync process and if you need assistance we guarantee a response&nbsp;within 48 hours. FLEXIBLE - FastBay guarantees many features that allows you to make a&nbsp;flexible site management&nbsp;that will suits all your needs. FAST - With our FastBay module your &#39;waiting times&#39; will be reduced beyond belief !&nbsp;Sync in a couple of minutes more than 5.000 products!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.3.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.4.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[194.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/748180-pprod/fastbay-ebay-marketplace-synchronization.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/748180-pbig/fastbay-ebay-marketplace-synchronization.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22666]]></id><name><![CDATA[onlinechat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Online Chat]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Поддержка и онлайн-чат]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With the Online Chat module developed by PrestaShop, you can finally offer an online chat system on your shop to have discussions with your customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/ru/support-online-chat/22666-online-chat.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/22666.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With the Online Chat module developed by PrestaShop, you can finally offer an online chat system on your shop to have discussions with your customers. This communication tool has become vital for e-commerce stores and allows you to create stronger relationships with your customers by guiding and advising them in their purchases in real time.   With this module that requires no subscription, improve your customer relations and your after-sales services, while increasing your conversion rate by up to 40%!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[No subscription needed; in just a few clicks you can set up your module and begin conversing with your online customers!&nbsp;You will find a simple, easy-to-use interface and a design that adapts perfectly to your site, in administration as for your store.&nbsp;With online conversations, you build a stronger, more human relationship with your customers and improve loyalty to your brand.&nbsp;You reduce the number of abandoned carts by answering your visitors&rsquo; questions directly.&nbsp;You save time in managing after-sales services by solving problems and requests live.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[94.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/752296-pprod/online-chat.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/752296-pbig/online-chat.jpg]]></big></cover></module></modules>